rvdmarkets.com 2014-04-02

# PRIVACY POLICY

 Mill Mall, Suite 6, Wickhams Cay 1, PO Box 3085,
    Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands
PRIVACY POLICY                                    ENG
                        2013

1. Introduction
RVD Markets Limited yours faithfully belongs to questions of confidentiality and considers saving of
Your personal confidential information by the main objective during implementation of all kinds of
activity.
Rendering services to our clients, we collect and store their personal data. For this reason we would
like to acquaint You with privacy policy which will be also applicable and in relation to You in case You
decide to use or have already use the services of our Company.
This policy from time to time can be revised for the purpose of the accounting of any changes in the
legislation and ensuring compliance to laws of technology and Company operations.
2 . Collecting and processing of personal information
2.1. The Company requests from the client information, which is necessary for opening personal
account for the client. The provision of such information is the indispensable condition allowing the
Company to protect interests of the client, and to the client to carry out various operations with use of
the personal account, without being afraid for safety of the assets.
The company also has the right to collect information which can promote improvement of an
assessment of needs and preferences of clients.
All information which is necessary for implementation of communications between the client and the
Company gathers directly from clients.
2.2. Information which we use:
2.2.1. Registration information, which you provided in the statement and other documents: surname,
name, middle name, postal address, e-mail, date of birth, occupation;
2.2.2. Information about transactions which are carried out with partners of our company and us, and
also data which we exchanged, such as the balance on accounts, our answers to questions, your trade
activity;
2.2.3. Information about notifications, news and promotions;
2.2.4. The identification information intended for confirmation of the personality: the passport or
driver's license, and also the data received in credit bureau, address agencies and other sources. It is    ENG
necessary to protect you and our reputation, and and prevent the activities of the laundering of funds.
2.3. Received from clients personal and contact information is used at verification of contact data and
the establishment of identity. The company also uses personal information of the client while account
creation, opening and setting up the trading account, delivery of code of activation and access
passwords. Contact information about the client helps the company to be improved with service and in
a timely manner to report to clients about additional products, opportunities and the actions which
are carried out by the company.
3 . Disclosure of client information to the third party
The Company has no right to disclose personal information of the client, except cases described below.
3.1. The company reserves the right to disclose personal information of the client to the third party if
that is demanded by regulating legislation, law enforcement and other government bodies. The
company also has the right to disclose the client information demanding granting in tax or credit
authorities or when it is necessary for protection of the rights and and property of the company.
3.2. If the third party receives any personal information about the client from the company, thus it
takes upon itself the duty of protection provided to them information in a manner similar to that
described in this Agreement.
3.3. The Company can use personal information of clients only for improvement quality of provided
services.
3.4. You have the right to refuse to provide information which will be requested by our experts.
However in case of your refusal we won't be able to give you full support and we can't guarantee high-
quality service of your accounts.
4. About cookies
4.1. Cookies are files that contain information used by the web site for traffic accounting (number of
visitors). The Company can get access to cookies of our sites located on your PC that allows to
determine which advertisement and resourses are most demanded for attracting potential clients, and
also to estimate your interest to various services and to define your activity on the site. All information
is strictly confidential and and is not associated with any specific client.

5. Security technology
5.1. Our company uses the modern technology of the secure connections (SSL) used for reliable saving
of information provided by you. The SSL technology provides reliable information security from
interception by the third parties. We are constantly improving the technology of security to prevent
unauthorized entry into the system.
6. Security and user account
6.1. Access to each account of the Client is carried out with the help of "Login" and "Password" and are
called as the "User account".
6.2. The Client agrees to be solely responsible for any use of the Service, committed with application of
his User account, as well as not to disclose the User account to third parties.
6.3. The client shall be solely responsible for any unauthorized use of the "User account", which will be
considered as as made by the Client. Any responsibility arising in this regard, falls on the Client. The
client is obliged to keep at any time privacy and confidentiality of the User account and make all efforts
for preservation of such privacy and confidentiality.
7. Safety of funds and operations of the clients
7.1. RVD Markets Limited isn't bank. We don't borrow and we don't grant loans to our clients. RVD
Markets Limited has no loans or debts on substandard assets.
7.2. The money of clients transferred to RVD Markets Limited, located on the separate account and
never used in other purposes.
7.3. Client funds are withdrawn from client accounts only as a result of trading activity of the client or
by the direct request of the client for withdrawal money.
8. Communications
8.1. While completing registration each client receives the letter by e-mail, confirming his registration.
The Company also can send to clients by e-mail information of any changes and new services, or             ENG
receive from clients electronic letters with questions and offers, this information isn't confidential.
8.2. The acceptance of this Agreement the client allows the company to use information received from
the client by e-mail, including various ideas, methods, marketing developments and a know-how,
without any subsequent obligations from the company. Exceptions include clients identification data.
8.3. The company has the right, review, save, or delete the correspondence with the client at its own
discretion.
8.4. The Company has the right to monitor internal communications clients to assess the quality of its
services.
